movieon.me 2016-11-27

# Privacy Policy - Movieon movies - Watch Movies Online Streaming in HD Quality

## Privacy Policy

We appreciate your interest in our website. For external links to external content while we can accept no liability Despite careful content control. The protection of your personal data in the collection, processing and use during your visit to our website is important to us. Your data will be protected under the law. Below is information on what data is recorded during your visit to our website and how it is used:

1\. Collection and processing of data  
Every access to our website and each download of a file on our website are logged. The storage serves internal system-related and statistical purposes. Be recorded: name of the file, date and time of access, data volume transferred, notification of successful download, web browser and requesting domain. Additionally, the IP addresses of the requesting computers are logged. Further personal data is only collected if you voluntarily as part of an inquiry or registration this information.

2\. Cookies  
The Internet pages use so-called cookies in several places. They serve to make our service more user-friendly, effective and safer. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer and saved by your browser. Most of the cookies we use are “session cookies”. They are automatically deleted after your visit. Cookies do not damage your computer and do not contain viruses.

3\. Use and disclosure of personal data  
If you provide us with personal data, we use it only to respond to your inquiries, to process contracts concluded with you and for technical administration. Your personal information will only be passed on to third parties or otherwise, if the purpose of the contract – is necessary for billing purposes as required or you have previously agreed – especially the transfer of order data to suppliers. You have the right to revoke your consent with future effect at any time. The deletion of stored personal data if you revoke your consent to storage, if their knowledge to fulfill the purpose for which the data is no longer required or if their storage is inadmissible for other legal reasons.

4\. Right  
Upon written request, we will inform you about the data stored about you. Security We are committed to your personal data by taking all technical and organizational possibilities so that they are not accessible by third parties. When communicating by e-mail the complete data security can not be guaranteed, so we recommend sending confidential information.

5\. Contact  
For questions about privacy and use of personal data, please use the Imprint stored contacts.  
Security Note:  
We strive to keep your personal data by taking all technical and organizational possibilities so that they are not accessible by third parties. When communicating by e-mail the complete data security can not be guaranteed, so we recommend sending confidential information.

6\. Privacy Policy for Usage of Facebook-Plugins (Like-Button)  
Our pages integrate plugins of the social network Facebook, 1601 South California Avenue, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA. The Facebook plugin, you agree to the Facebook logo or the “Like-Button” (“Like”) on our side. You will find an overview of Facebook-plugins here: http://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/

When visiting our pages, the plugin establishes a connection between your browser and the Facebook server is established. Facebook receives the information that you have with your IP address visited our site. If you click on the Facebook “Like” button while you are logged into your Facebook account, you can link the content of our pages on your Facebook profile. Thereby Facebook can correlate your visit of our site with your user account. We point out that we as providers of the sites no knowledge of the content of the transmitted data and use them through Facebook. For more information, please see the privacy policy of Facebook at http://de-de.facebook.com/policy.php

If you do not wish that Facebook can assign to visit our pages to your Facebook user account, please log out of your Facebook user account.
